Amen.
Hello, brothers and sisters.
Happy Wednesday, everybody.
Yes, how's everyone doing today?
I see here we've got Jim, Sister Nia,
Pamela, Tawana.
We've
got Alberta, Yanis, Angela, Dracos, Warren,
Debra, Janet,
Enrique, and my dear brother, Alfonso.
and more and more brothers and
sisters are slowly joining us.
We have Ur and Fletcher as well.
Welcome, everybody.
Really happy to see everyone here.
So my dear brothers and sisters, I
hope everyone is having a great day so far.
Okay.
So brothers and sisters, through our
fellowship yesterday, we came to
understand that the Lord will come back in
the flesh, and will come to carry out the
work of judgment and the work of
purification.
And we know that it's only by accepting
God's work of judgment through his words
in the
last days that we can truly be cleansed and
have an
opportunity to enter the kingdom of heaven.
But yet some believers, they believe that
well, since the Lord Jesus was redeemed
through his crucifixion, that God's work
of salvation is already complete.
Right?
So they don't understand why God still needs to carry out the work of
judgment.
Right?
Which we already talked about that
yesterday.
Which let me ask you, brothers and
sisters, for everyone that was here
yesterday, why does God still need to
carry out the work of judgment?
Does anyone remember?
Is it A, to purify and to cleanse us of
Satan's poison, such as the greed,
the selfishness, the lust?
Or
do you think it's B, I already believe in
the
Lord, I know he's not going to do anything.
Or C, you're not quite sure.
Does anyone remember?
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Hey, good remembering.
Good remembering, everybody.
That's right.
A is definitely the correct answer.
Right?
A is definitely the correct answer,
brothers and sisters.
We got to go through the purification.
Right?
We need the purification because we've got
a lot of Satan's poisons inside of us.
We live through a vicious cycle of
sinning, confessing, sinning, confessing.
And you know that God cannot put us into
the kingdom of heaven.
If he did, what is Satan going to say?
Satan is going to say, well, you're
allowing sinners into your kingdom.
You should let me too.
Right?
Satan's going to say, I corrupted them.
So you have to put me in there too.
But you know, it doesn't work like that.
It doesn't work like that, brothers and
sisters.
So to help us enter the kingdom of heaven,
God has a lot of work to do.
Right?
He's got to cleanse and purify mankind.
And he does that by expressing a lot,
a lot of truth.
Hence why the Lord said, I have yet many
things to say to you.
Meaning he's still got more words to say,
brothers and sisters.
So tonight, we're going to talk about the
three stages of God's work.
We've only experienced two stages.
But what about the third one?
Right?
The third one is the one that we're
waiting for.
And why is the third stage the most
important one?
All right.
Hopefully tonight's fellowship will help
you have a deeper understanding,
okay, brothers and sisters, in God's 6,000
year management plan.
Because if we only accept one of God's
work and you fail to recognize the other,
then aren't you repeating the same mistake
the Pharisees did?
Aren't you clinging to the old work of God
and rejecting the Lord's second coming?
Yeah.
So to avoid that, let's come together,
right?
Let's look at God's management plan,
okay, brothers and sisters, and let us see
how God carries out his work to fully save
humanity. Amen
So with
that being said, let's go ahead and let's
quiet our hearts
and let us come before God in prayer.
Okay?
So let's close our eyes, bow our head,
and let's pray.
Amen.
Dear Heavenly
Father, Almighty God, we thank you so much
for bringing
us together tonight once again, dear God.
And
even though we come from different places
all around
the world, dear God, but here we are.
Here we are, dear Lord.
We want to experience your words.
We want to learn.
We want to learn your work of the last
days, dear God.
So thank
you for making a way for us to gather here
together
to learn more about your plan of salvation.
We are grateful for this opportunity to be
in your presence, dear Lord, and to seek
the truth together with you.
Lord, we also want to lift up those who
have not yet joined.
Please
reach out to them, touch their hearts, and
lead them
to your truth and your light, dear God.
May they come
to know your love, and may they come to
join us on
this wonderful journey of faith, dear God.
Last night, we learned a very important
topic about the judgment.
And we know that your judgment of the
believers is not a punishment,
dear God, because your judgment starts at
the house of God with the believers.
So we could see that your judgment is not
a condemnation.
It's not a punishment,
but it is your loving way to cleanse
us from sin and
to prepare us for your kingdom, dear God.
So please help us to see this judgment as
an expression.
Of your
mercy, and a love, and love, a process that
we all need
in order to truly be changed and made new.
So tonight, dear God, we ask you to open
our hearts and our minds.
Help us to listen with sincerity,
and help us to understand your words
deeply,
and help us to draw closer to you through
everything
that we hear and that we share.
In Jesus' name, we pray.
Amen.
Amen. Brothers and sisters.
All praise be to God. Amen!
So, my beloved brothers and sisters. Let's get started, okay?
Now, all of us, we are all believers. Yes, we are, okay?
And we have all read the Bible
Does anyone know how many stages of God's work are actually in the Bible?
Does anyone know this question?
How many stages of work are in the Bible?
Welcome Chris.
Yeah. How many stages of work are in the Bible?
Someone give me a number.
Yeah, give me a number, brothers and
sisters.
Yeah, how many stages?
Would you say one, two, three?
Okay, I see different numbers.
I see seven.
I see three.
Okay.
Now, let me tell you the actual answer.
Oh, Cody.
Cody got it.
There's actually only two, brothers and
sisters.
Yeah, there's only two.
There is the Old Testament and the New
Testament.
That's a tricky question, wasn't it?
Right?
Those are the two stages that God has
already done.
You see, the Old Testament records how
Jehovah God issued the laws and commandment.
That was the first stage of God's work,
the Old Testament, the age of law.
And the
New Testament records the Lord Jesus being
crucified
as a sin offering to redeem humanity.
And that was the second stage of God's
work.
Can we all agree?
Do we all agree so far?
There's only two.
The Old Testament and the New Testament.
Isn't that right, brothers and sisters?
Welcome, Nelda.
Welcome.
I don't know how to pronounce that name.
I'm so sorry.
That was easy enough.
It was easy, wasn't it, Pamela?
We made it so hard.
But it's easy.
There was only two.
The Old Testament and the New Testament,
my beloved brothers and sisters.
Only two, okay?
That's okay, Thomas.
That's okay.
Brothers and sisters.
After these two stages of work,
right?
Is God's work done?
Is it over?
Does that mean we can directly enter God's
kingdom?
Exactly, Sister Tawana.
Amen, Brother Michael.
Amen, Maureen.
No, absolutely not.
So, amen, Dracos.
Amen, Angela.
Absolutely not.
So, remember, from our fellowship
yesterday, over the past few days,
we should be clear by now.
Having our sins forgiven does not mean all
of us have stopped sinning.
Hello, we still sin.
Every day.
And it definitely does not mean we have
achieved salvation.
Right?
Yeah, that's right, brothers and sisters.
It is not over.
It isn't over.
Because if it was over, all of us would
have been in the kingdom already.
But why isn't it over?
Because our sinful nature.
You remember, brothers and sisters?
Our sinful nature hasn't been resolved
yet.
That is
why all of us are stuck in a constant cycle
of sinning,
confessing, sinning, and confessing.
You see, a humanity that sins and
confesses.
All the time.
Obviously, cannot enter the kingdom of
heaven.
The kingdom of heaven is holy.
It's righteous.
It's pure.
But we're not.
And that is why the Lord prophesied that
he's coming back.
He's
coming back to carry out the last stage of his work
which was yesterday's topic.
The work of judgment and cleansing.
To finally save us from sin once and for
all.
So, let's do some more math.
If in the Bible, God has already done two
stages of work, right?
And God still needs to come back as the Son
of Man to carry out the work of judgment.
In total, how many stages are there,
brothers and sisters?
Welcome, Sister Wendy.
In total, how many stages are there then?
That's right, Sister.
Amen.
There you go, brothers and sisters.
Now you're getting the hang of it.
Yeah, there's three.
In total, there's three.
So, yeah, God does his work of saving
humanity in three stages.
So,
the three stages of God's work literally
complete
God's management plan to save all of us.
But I know you're probably like,
what, Sister Thelma?
Why does he need three stages of work to
save us?
Well, first of all, I want to tell you the
aim of the three stages of work.
Then we're
going to read a spiritual passage tonight
so
that you can understand why there is three.
So,
here it says, the aim of the three stages
of
work is the salvation of all mankind.
This means the complete salvation of man
from the power of Satan.
Amen.
So,
as you can see, brothers and sisters, God
wants
us to save us from the power of Satan.
Now, let's listen to another spiritual
enlightenment to help us understand why
God has a 6,000-year management plan,
right?
What is God's plan to save humanity?
Let's listen together.
The 6,000 years of work of God's
management are divided into three stages.
The age of law, the age of grace,
and the age of kingdom.
These three stages of work are all for the
sake of mankind's salvation.
Which
is to say, they are for the salvation
of
a mankind that has been severely corrupted.
By Satan.
At the same time, however, they are also
so that God may do battle with Satan.
Thus, just as the work of salvation is
divided into three stages, so the battle
with Satan is also divided into three
stages.
And these two aspects of God's work are
conducted simultaneously.
The battle with Satan is actually for the sake of mankind's salvation.
And because the work of mankind's
salvation is not something that can be
successfully
completed in a single stage.
The battle with Satan
is also divided into phases and periods.
And war is waged
upon Satan in accordance with the needs of man
and the extent of Satan's corruption of him.
In the work of man's
salvation,
Three stages have been carried out,
which is to say that the battle with Satan
has been split into three stages prior to
the complete defeat of Satan.
Yet the inner truth of the entire work of
the battle with Satan is that its effects
are achieved through bestowing grace upon
man and becoming a sin offering of man,
forgiving the sins of man, conquering man,
and making man perfect.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Did you get that?
Did you get that, everybody?
You could see here, right, from these
spiritual words, you could see that God's
work of saving humanity is basically a war
against Satan.
And brothers and sisters, who are they
fighting for?
Who are they fighting for?
Does anyone know?
Who is God and Satan fighting for,
brothers and sisters?
Yeah, who are they fighting for?
Does anyone know?
Ah, brothers and sisters, as you could
see.
Exactly, they're fighting for us.
Yeah, brothers and sisters, it is a war
against Satan.
They're battling for us.
Right?
Where
God is trying to save us away from sinning,
where
Satan is trying to corrupt us into sinning.
They're in a battle.
So through these three stages of work,
God saves humanity from the domain of
Satan step by step, so we can be
completely gained by God.
And ever since humanity was corrupted by
Satan, you know sin entered into the world.
And brothers and sisters, because of sin,
mankind dies.
The only reason why we all die is because
we sin.
We sin.
So to completely save us, right,
from sin, so we stop sinning and can
actually live
forever under God's care and protection,
God
started his 6,000 year management plan.
Welcome Javonte.
Yeah.
This means, brothers and sisters,
he launched his three stages of work.
the moment
mankind was corrupted by Satan.
Why?
Because at the end of the day,
brothers and sisters, you have to
understand,
God could have probably destroyed
all
of humanity and started all over again.
But did he do that?
Welcome Anthony.
Welcome Foileen.
Did he do that?
No, he didn't do that, brothers and
sisters.
Because God loves humanity.
So rather than destroy us, he has to teach
us the truth.
And that's when God's management plan
began.
So first, he teaches people to know sin
through the age of law.
Then, he redeems humanity from sin through
the age of grace.
And finally, he completely resolves the
root cause of why we sin, right?
Meaning, he gets rid of our sins once and
for all through the age of kingdom,
through the judgment work.
So as you can see, each stage of God's
work is actually very meaningful.
Every stage is essential for his-to his
management plan in order to save us.
And it's all necessary
steps for corrupt humanity to cast off
and break away from
sin, break away from Satan's influence.
So brothers and sisters, we're going
to break these three stages down, okay?
I want
all of you to really grasp and understand
why
God carries his work in three stages.
How does God save us from Satan's domain?
Let's begin with
the first stage of God's work
which is called what?
The age of law.
Right?
It is called the age of law, brothers and
sisters.
Now think about it.
Why was the first stage of God's work to
save mankind the work of issuing the laws?
It is because in the very beginning,
humans were like newborn babies.
They didn't know how to worship God.
They didn't even know how to live on
earth.
They didn't even understand the most basic
moral standard.
For example, they didn't even know that
murder or stealing was sin.
They didn't even...
so what did they do brothers and sisters?
they just sin again and again and again and again
and that really offended God.
You see, brothers and sisters,
it really offended God.
So to keep humanity away from sin,
to help them live a normal life,
well, of course, what did God do?
He began his first work on earth.
The work of the age of law.
So what did God do?
He issued laws and commandments to teach
people how to live on earth.
And what did he give?
He gave
a lot of basic concept of sin.
You know, the laws and commandments.
You see, brothers and sisters,
what are the laws and commandments?
One of them is that you shall have no
other God before me.
Right?
Also, you shall not make any graven image.
Remember the Sabbath day.
Keep it holy.
Honor your father and mother.
You shall not kill.
You shall not commit adultery.
You shall not steal.
you shall not bear false witness against your neighbors
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
These laws clearly showed people what they
could and could not do.
It laid out the ways to follow and rules
to keep at that time.
It lets people know what was right and
what was wrong.
Isn't that right, brothers and sisters?
And they had to offer a sin offering for
their atonement.
So, if people violated
certain laws and decrees, well, you
already know God's
wrath and punishment would strike them.
We talked about this yesterday,
right, brothers and sisters?
What would happen?
They would either be stoned to death or
burned by the fire from heaven.
You see, the Israelites, they all
experienced God's majesty and his wrath,
as well as his care and mercy.
They all recognized that Jehovah God is the one true God that created the heavens and the earth and all things.
And they were
so because of this they all fear Jehovah
they kept His law, they live a normal on earth, they worshipped Him.
and they were able to live before God.
and that was the result of God's work in the Age of Law.
Now think about this.
Think about something, brothers and
sisters.
What would have happened to humanity if
God hadn't done the work of the Age of Law?
Does anyone know?
What would have happened to humanity?
Take a wild guess.
What if there was no laws and
commandments, brothers and sisters,
to hold mankind down?
You tell me.
What would have happened to humanity if
God hadn't done the work of the Age of Law?
Anybody know?
What would have happened?
I see Anthony's typing.
Yeah, what do you think would have
happened?
Think about it.
If there was
no law, if there was no commandments,
what would have really
happened to mankind, brothers and sisters?
Ah, exactly.
Chaos, Pamela says.
Destroyed, Draco says.
A lot of chaos and sin.
Cody says perish.
Anthony
says a lot of... Yeah, we would have
all
been destroyed, brothers and sisters.
I agree with all of you.
Because if there was no laws
to keep us in check, if there was no...
if we didn't have God's
guidance, we would have all been dead.
Right?
We would have all been snatched away from
Satan in no time.
So as you can see, God issuing the laws
and commandments was absolutely critical.
It was important.
So the work in the Age of Law,
it showed people that they sinned
constantly and they really needed a sin
offering to atone for their sins.
So this stage of God's work not only led
humanity onto the right track of life,
but it also laid the foundation.
It paved the way for the work of God.
Redemption that God was going to do in the
Age of Grace.
But hold up.
Wait a minute.
Let me ask you a question.
When God
completed his work in the Age of Law,
does it mean that
God's work of saving mankind has ended?
Is it over brothers and sisters?
Is it?
Ah, amen.
Amen everybody.
Absolutely not.
Absolutely not, brothers and sisters.
You see, the first stage of God's work was
only the age of law.
It was the work of issuing the law.
It was to teach man to know sin.
But let me tell you something.
Later in the age of law, all of humanity
was so deeply corrupted by Satan.
They were sinning more and more and more.
And the law could no longer control them
anymore.
They didn't even have enough sin offering.
And they were all facing condemnation and
execution under the law.
They were all calling out to God in their
pain.
So God personally became flesh as the Lord
Jesus.
And he performed the work of redemption,
beginning the second stage of God's work.
What is that work called?
The age of grace, brothers and sisters.
The age of grace.
When Jesus came, he ended the age of law.
You see?
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Let's go ahead and
let's listen to a short passage so we can
understand what exactly
was happening during the age of grace.
All right.
Very short one.
Here we go.
Would any brother or sister actually like
to read it?
It starts with during the age of grace.
Anybody feel like reading this one?
Really sure?
No?
If not, I've got an audio we can listen
to.
Okay.
Hello?
Oh, does someone have their mic open?
All right.
Let's listen.
Don't worry.
Then, during the age of grace, Jesus
came to redeem the whole of fallen mankind.
And not only the Israelites.
He showed mercy and loving kindness to
man.
The Jesus that man saw in the age of
grace, was filled with loving kindness,
and was always loving toward man,
for he had come to save humanity from sin.
He was able
to forgive men their sins,
until his crucifixion
completely redeemed mankind from sin.
During this period, God appeared before
man with mercy and loving kindness.
That is, he became a sin offering for man,
and was crucified for the sins of man,
so that they might forever be forgiven.
Amen.
No problem, Sister Foilene.
No worries at all.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
So, look at that, right?
When the Lord Jesus lived among us,
he taught us to confess, to repent,
to love each other as ourselves,
to be forgiving, right?
To love God with all our heart,
soul, and mind.
To worship God in spirit and in truth.
Jesus' words
also showed people what God's will was,
gave them a
distant goal, and direction in their faith.
You see, this was a step beyond the restrictions
of the law and the rules of the law.
He also showed many signs and wonders,
healing the sick, driving out demons,
forgiving our sins.
You see, Jesus, he was so full of
tolerance and patience.
Everyone could feel God's love and mercy.
Everyone could see his loveliness.
Everyone could draw closer to God.
But in the end, he was nailed to the
cross, serving as an eternal sin offering,
forgiving our sins, once and for all.
And after
that, people just needed to confess and
repent to the
Lord in order to have their sins forgiven.
And they wouldn't be condemned or punished
under the law.
You see, we, at that time, many of them
were able to come before God in prayer and
enjoy everything that God had bestowed
upon them.
So you could see, right?
Clearly, Jesus' work of redemption has
been one of the greatest blessings for
humanity, allowing people to continue to
survive and thrive even until today.
But let me ask you brothers and sisters.
Hello, brother Mitch.
Welcome.
After
the Lord Jesus was crucified, do we still
need
to make animal offerings when we sin?
Jesus was crucified.
Do we still need to make animal offerings
when we sin, brothers and sisters?
What do you think?
Amen.
Get sharing.
No, of course not.
Right?
Because the Lord, Jesus, was crucified for all of humanity.
He became our sin.
He was the ultimate sin offering.
That's why
today you don't see people going to a farm
to find an
animal to give to God as a burnt offering.
He was the unblemished lamb.
So we don't need to do that anymore.
Because we confess now.
We repent.
Our sins are forgiven.
And that's why none of us are condemned or
put to death because of the Law.
So as you can see, brothers and sisters,
being forgiven of our sin, being saved for
our faith,
I'm sorry, it only means being forgiven
of our
sin and not being condemned under the Law.
So we are saved from the condemnation of
the Law!
You see?
So the Lord Jesus, brothers and sisters,
He was the eternal sin offering.
He only forgives our sins.
He only forgave our sins.
All right?
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
So the second stage of God's work,
which we have already passed through,
it is the age of grace.
The work is the crucifixion.
The result was to forgive mankind's sin.
All right?
It was to forgive mankind's sin.
But I do have to ask you all a question.
Brothers and sisters, after the Lord Jesus
finished the work of redemption,
did that mean God's work of salvation is
over?
A. God's work of salvation is not over.
Since we still sin, we need God to do more
work to save us.
Or B.
God's work of salvation is finished.
We just need to wait for God to take us
into the kingdom of heaven.
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Is it over?
Is it really over?
No, right?
Amen, everybody.
Absolutely not.
It is not over.
You see, because a lot of people will say,
when the Lord Jesus said on the cross,
it is over, it is finished.
Doesn't that mean that God's work of
salvation is done?
Why do we still need more work?
But brothers
and sisters, let me tell you what the
true meaning
of it is finished actually refers to.
It didn't mean that God's work of
salvation was done.
When
the Lord said, it is finished, he was just
saying
the work of the crucifixion was done.
That God's work of redemption was
complete.
He definitely did not mean that God's
entire work of saving humanity was finished.
You see, the age of grace has lasted for
2000 years.
And almost all believers think that just
because the Lord was crucified to redeem
humanity, that God's work of salvation is
over.
It ain't over.
It's not over.
Right?
People think, oh, when the Lord comes
back, he's just going to raise us up in
the air and bring us into the kingdom of
heaven.
But is that really going to happen?
Because you
tell me, brothers and sisters, it's true,
our sins are forgiven
after we have believed in the Lord.
But did the Lord Jesus completely get rid
of our sinful nature?
Is our sinful nature transformed?
Is our sinful nature cleansed,
brothers and sisters?
There you go.
Brothers and sisters, you have a great,
great, great understanding.
Absolutely not.
Because look at that.
Even until today, what are we doing?
Still sinning.
Right?
You see, the Holy Spirit worked during the
age of grace for 2000 years.
Has humanity truly come to know God?
Think about it, brothers and sisters.
Have you truly come to know God?
Would you say that you have true knowledge
of God today?
Have you reached the point where you no
longer sin?
Has your corruption really been cleansed?
I think the answer is all no.
I agree with you, Brother Anthony.
Right?
No.
So what does this show us?
It shows us that although
people in the age of grace experience
the work of the
Holy Spirit, they still cannot escape sin.
They still cannot attain holiness.
So therefore, the fact that humanity has
gone through 2000s of years of the
redemption work of the age of grace
without breaking free from sin is enough
to prove how deeply mankind has been
corrupted by Satan.
You see, some people say, but I have
believed in God for 20 or 30 years.
If I have believed in God my whole life,
I will be able to escape my sinful nature.
But this viewpoint is not correct.
Humanity has experienced Jesus' work of
redemption for 2000 years.
But yet, not a single person has achieved
a change in disposition.
So therefore, brothers and sisters,
we need God to bring the work of judgment
and the work of purification in the last
days.
Because remember, what are the
requirements to enter God's kingdom?
Isn't it to be holy?
Isn't it to obey God and live out the word
of God?
Isn't it to be holy and be purified?
Isn't it to stop sinning and to live free
from sin?
Absolutely.
Right?
It's all the above.
Take
a look at the picture that I'm about to
send
to you right now, brothers and sisters.
Have a look.
Sin is our outer behavior.
Like lying, blasphemy, slander,
theft, jealousy.
Adultery.
Those are all sin.
But what about the sinful nature?
What's deeply hidden inside of us?
Arrogance, vanity, hypocrisy,
self-righteousness, greed, selfishness.
That's all inside of us.
You see, even though the Lord Jesus was
crucified as our sin offering to redeem
us, remember, our sinful nature was not
cleansed.
We're all driven by the sinful nature.
We live in our corrupt dispositions every
single day.
We still constantly lie.
We fight for fame and gain.
We feel jealous.
We get into arguments.
We act arrogant and self-righteous.
And even though we don't want to,
right?
We don't want to, but we still do it.
Because it's in our sinful nature.
We want to be tolerant.
We want to be patient.
But we just can't do it.
We want to love others as ourselves,
but we can't.
We can't put it into practice.
And loving and submitting to the Lord,
that's even tougher.
So even though people have enjoyed much of
God's grace and had their sins forgiven,
they still don't know how to fear God and
shun evil.
They still don't know how to follow God's
way.
And no matter how devout, patient,
or loving someone may seem on the outside,
the root of their resistance to God is
still there.
Completely unchanged.
You see, people have no path or power to
cast off sin.
They're
just stuck in a vicious cycle of
sinning
by the day and confessing by the night.
So now think.
Can someone living in sin like this really
be considered saved?
Are they qualified to get into the kingdom
of heaven?
No.
Absolutely not.
Right?
Exactly, Sister Pamela.
It's just as the Lord Jesus said.
Truly, truly, I say to you, whoever
commits sin is the servant of sin.
And the servant stays not in the house
forever, but the son stays ever.
John 8, 34-35.
You shall therefore be holy, for I am
holy.
Leviticus 11, 45.
Holiness without which no man shall see
the Lord.
Hebrews 12, 45.
Don't we have a righteous and holy God?
How could
he possibly allow people who constantly
sin
and resist him to enter his kingdom?
So, after finishing the work of
redemption, the Lord Jesus prophesied
multiple, multiple times that he would
come back.
That he's coming back to do a stage of
judgment work in the last days.
To completely cleanse and save humanity.
To bring his people into his kingdom.
It's just as the Lord prophesied.
He said, I have yet many things to say to
you, but you cannot bear them now.
However, when he, the spirit of truth,
is come, he will guide you into all truth.
John 16, 12-13.
Sanctify them through your truth.
Your word is truth.
John 17, 17.
He that rejects me and accepts not my
words has one that judges him.
The word that I have spoken, the same
shall judge him in the last day.
John 12, 48.
Isn't it clear, brothers and sisters?
When you really focus in the word of the
Lord, you could really have a path forward.
When the Lord comes back, he's going to
express more truth.
He's going to do a stage of judgment work.
To guide his people into all truth.
So that means he's going to completely
save us from sin.
Deliver us from Satan's influence.
And bring us into God's kingdom.
And this is a stage of work that God
actually already planned long ago.
And that's his final work.
There's no more work after this,
brothers and sisters.
You see, this stage of work, it's not about
issuing laws and commandments anymore.
It's not about giving humanity abundant
grace.
Instead, it is the work of chastisement and judgment.
It's about disciplining mankind now.
And only the work of chastisement and
judgment can get rid of Satan's poison and sinful nature.
Resolve our corruptions.
And completely gain humanity.
And finally, conclude God's 6,000 year
management plan.
And you know what this stage of work is
called, brothers and sisters?
Exactly, brother Michael.
It's his management plan.
And the third stage in which he perfects
people, it is called the age of kingdom.
That's right, brothers and sisters.
It is the age of kingdom.
You see, my beloved brothers and sisters,
what is the age of kingdom?
Brothers and sisters, the age of kingdom
is what?
It's the training of the kingdom.
This is where God will finally train us
how to be holy.
Teach us how to be righteous.
We still have to go through the training of
the kingdom in order to get to the kingdom.
Isn't that right, brothers and sisters?
Because think about it, brothers and
sisters.
Let's say you play a sport.
You play soccer.
You know, FIFA World Cup is going on.
If you never go to practice, do you think
the coach is going to put you in the field?
Brothers and sisters?
If
you never attend the practice, do you think
the
coach is going to put you in the field?
No, right?
Exactly.
Now,
the Lord prophesied that he's coming back
in
order to carry out the work of judgment.
If you do not accept his judgment work,
do you think you can enter his kingdom?
Once again, big no-no.
Big no-no.
Ain't that right, brothers and sisters?
Exactly.
That's why we've got to go through the
training of the kingdom.
All right?
So, let's listen to two spiritual passages
together.
Why the training of the kingdom,
the age of kingdom, is so important.
Okay?
I'll wait till we all get it.
And I'll play.
I'll play the audio.
Though Jesus did much work among man,
he only completed the redemption of all
mankind
and became man's sin offering and
did not
rid man of all his corrupt disposition.
Fully saving man from the influence of
Satan not only required Jesus to take on
the sins of man as the sin offering,
but also required God to do greater work
to completely rid man of his disposition,
which has been corrupted by Satan.
And so, after man was forgiven his sins,
God has returned to flesh to lead man into
the new age and begun the work of
chastisement and judgment.
And this work has brought man into a
higher realm.
All
those who submit under his dominion shall
enjoy
higher truth and receive greater blessings.
They shall truly live in the light and
shall gain the truth, the way, and the life.
Amen.
One more.
Let's listen to the second one.
Amen, amen.
Here we go, brothers and sisters.
By means of this work of judgment and
chastisement, man will fully come to know
the filthy and
corrupt essence within his own self
and he will be
able to change completely and become clean.
Only in this way can man become worthy to
return before the throne of God.
All the work done this day is so that man
can be made clean and be changed.
Through judgment and chastisement by the
word, as well as through refinement,
man can purge away his corruption and be
made pure.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Look at that, right?
Why?
Why does God need to do the work of
judgment?
It's
because the Lord Jesus' work of redemption,
it
didn't get rid of our sinful nature.
It didn't completely save us from Satan's
corruption.
So God's work of saving humanity,
it's not over.
He still needs to do a stage of judgment
work to completely cleanse and save people.
So from this, we can see that the Lord
Jesus' work of redemption was simply
paving the way for the work of judgment in
the last days.
And
the work of judgment, it is the last,
most
crucial part of God's work of salvation.
It is the only path for humanity to be
saved and enter the kingdom of heaven.
So
speaking of judgment, brothers and sisters,
does
anyone remember how God judges us?
But before we talk about that,
let me just give you a diagram.
Jesus' work of redemption only forgave
mankind's sin.
Man still has sinful nature.
So man needs to accept the work of
judgment.
Man needs to be purified in order to enter
the kingdom of heaven.
You see that, my dear brothers and
sisters?
It's greatly, greatly important.
Amen, Cody.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Amen.
So, my dear brothers and sisters,
does anyone remember?
What does God use to do the work of
judgment to cleanse us?
What does he use?
Who remembers?
How are we going to be cleansed?
With what?
I think some of you
guys... Ah, there you go, Brother Michael.
Brother Michael says we will be cleansed
with the truth.
Not natural disasters, Brother Warren.
Natural disasters can kill you.
Only the word of God can cleanse you,
my dear brother.
Only the truth can set you free.
You see?
Remember, Brother Warren.
The Lord did say, I have yet many things
to say to you.
But you cannot bear them now.
However, when he, the spirit of truth,
has come, he will guide you into all truth.
And you shall know the truth.
The truth shall set you free.
Sanctify them through your truth.
Your word is truth.
Right?
What is sanctify?
Let me type.
Sanctify.
Brothers and sisters, sanctify means to
cleanse.
To be made holy.
That's what sanctify means.
To be cleansed.
To be purified, brothers and sisters.
Now, let me ask you another question.
Hopefully you all remember.
What words will the Lord use for his work
of judgment in the last days to cleanse us?
Is it A.
The words in the Bible that we have been
reading.
Is it B.
New words outside of the Bible when he
returns in the last days.
Or C.
I'm not quite sure.
Does anyone remember, brothers and
sisters?
Where are the new words?
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
That's right.
The new words, right?
B is the correct answer.
Good sharing.
Jim, Michael, Draco, Warren, Alberta,
Cody, Pamela, Anthony, Michael.
Amen.
Good sharing, brothers and sisters.
Welcome back, Brother Clifton.
Welcome back.
Yeah, brothers and sisters.
The correct answer is, in fact,
B.
Remember, the Lord says, I have yet many
things to say to you.
You see, these many things are words the
Lord has never spoken.
They are words we've never heard before.
And they're exactly what the Lord will
express when he comes back.
So could these words possibly have been
recorded in the Bible ahead of time?
Of course not.
The Bible mentions the sealed book many
times.
Right?
Especially here.
Have a look.
In the book of Revelation.
Look what it says.
It says, And I saw in the right hand of
him that sat on a throne a book written
within and on the backside sealed with
seven seals.
And I saw a strong
angel proclaiming with a loud voice, Who is
worthy to open the
book and to lose the seven seals thereof?
And no man
in heaven, nor in earth, neither under the
earth, was able
to open the book, neither to look thereon.
And I wept much, because no man was found
worthy to open and to read the book,
neither to look thereon.
And one of the elders said to me,
Weep not.
Behold, the Lion of the tribe of Judah,
the Root of David, has prevailed to open
the book, and to lose the seven seals
thereof.
Also,
but you, O Daniel, shut up the words and
seal
the book, even to the time of the end.
Many shall run to and fro, and knowledge
shall be increased.
And the third one reads, And he said,
Go your way, Daniel, for the words are
closed up and sealed till the time of the
end.
Many shall be purified, and made white,
and tried.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
All praises be to God.
Right?
So we could see, first and foremost,
the seal book, it's sealed.
it is sealed
Nobody can open it.
Especially 2,000 years ago, because it wasn't time.
So
God prophesied that this book,
the seal book,
can only be opened in the time of the end.
And it will be the return of Lord Jesus
that will bring his new words to mankind.
And the purpose of the seal book is to
cleanse us.
To purify us.
Brothers and sisters.
Right?
So we could see.
The seal book is obviously not the Bible
that we read every day.
It's not even the book of Revelation.
The Bible has been around for thousands of
years.
We can open it.
We can read it whenever we want.
But the little scroll in the new book is a
new book that the Lord will bring.
Right?
Because
you have to understand the Bible only
contains
the words God spoke in the past.
The seal book is not the Bible that we
read today.
There are words that God expresses upon
his second coming.
There are words God has never spoken
before.
There are words that we have never heard
So naturally, obviously God's new words
cannot be recorded in the Bible.
Isn't that right?
So in the last days, the Lord will return
to express new words and open the
seal book in order to carry out the work of
judgment.
Let's listen to another passage of words,
okay brothers and sisters?
Here we go.
Let's listen to another passage of spiritual
words to help us understand even more.
What will these words do for us?
Christ of the last days uses
Christ of the last days uses a variety of truths to teach man,
To expose the substance of man,
and to dissect the words and deeds of man.
These words comprise various truths,
such as man's duty, how man should obey
God, how man should be loyal to God,
how man ought to live out normal humanity,
as well as the wisdom and the disposition
of God, and so on.
These words are all directed at the
substance of man and his corrupt disposition.
In particular, the words that expose how
man spurns God are spoken in regard to how
man is an embodiment of Satan and an enemy
force against God.
In undertaking
his work of judgment, God does not
simply make
clear the nature of man with a few words.
He exposes, deals with, and prunes over
the long term.
All these different methods of exposure,
dealing and pruning, cannot be substituted
with ordinary words, but with the truth of
which man is utterly bereft.
Only methods such as these can be called
judgment.
Only through judgment of this kind can man
be subdued and thoroughly convinced about God
and moreover gain true knowledge of
God.
What the work of judgment brings about is
man's understanding of the true face of God
and the truth about his own
rebelliousness.
The work of judgment allows man to gain
much understanding of the will of God,
of the purpose of God's work, and of the
mysteries that are incomprehensible to him.
It also allows man to recognize and know
his corrupt essence and the roots of his
corruption, as well as to discover the
ugliness of man.
These effects are all brought about by the
work of judgment, for the essence of this
work is actually
the work of opening up the truth, the way,
and the life
of God to all those who have faith in him.
This work is the work of judgment done by
God.
Amen!
Amen, brothers and sisters!
So we can see, right?
In the final stage of God's work,
God is going to use the truth,
because God knows mankind doesn't seek the
truth.
So he's going to express a lot of words to
call out his people.
Because that's why the Bible says,
My sheep hear my voice.
Faith comes by hearing.
He that has an ear, let him hear.
Behold, I stand at the door and out,
if any man hear my voice.
He's going to express a lot of words,
brothers and sisters.
And these words will judge and help us get
rid of our sin.
You see, the truth of God's words is like
a great light.
Almost like a mirror.
It's only through
the revelation and the judgment of the word
of God can we see how
deeply rooted our sinful nature really is.
And only then can we truly come to know
and hate ourselves.
Consciously put the truth into practice
and act according to the word of God.
Allowing his words to become the standard
of our lives.
And
at that point, our sinful nature is truly cleansed
by the truth that God expresses.
We're completely renewed and transformed.
Becoming new people created by God.
Isn't that the whole point?
New people created by God.
Right?
The mankind that God has originally
created that has lost their own function.
People who can practice the word of God in
everything they do.
You see,
such a person is ultimately cleansed and is
someone who will
survive and who will enter God's kingdom.
So this shows us how incredibly important
the work of judgment that God does with
the truth in the age of kingdom for all of
humanity how important it is.
Now, if people can accept God's work of
judgment in the last days, yes,
their corruptions will be cleansed.
They'll stop sinning.
They'll stop resisting God.
They'll be able to submit to God.
Love God unconditionally.
And only then can God's work of saving
humanity finally come to a close.
That's when the 6,000 year management plan
of God will come to a successful end.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Amen.
So, in summary, there are three stages in
God's work.
The age of law, which was to issue the laws
and commandments so mankind can know sin.
And
if you want to read all of God's work in
the
age of law, where are you going to find it?
In the Old Testament.
And then we have the second stage of God's
work.
The age of grace.
The work of redemption. To forgive our sins
If you want to know how Jesus redeemed
humanity, what are you going to read?
The New Testament.
But how are you going to know the third
stage of God's work?
The age of kingdom.
To experience the judgment.
To have our sinful natures purified.
You can't read the Old Testament.
That's Jehovah God's work of issuing the
laws and commandments.
You can't read the New Testament.
That's Jesus' work of redemption.
So what are you going to read?
The seal book, brothers and sisters.
The sealed book.
You see?
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Everyone clear so far?
Everyone clear so far, brothers and
sisters?
Amen, Amen.
What about the rest?
Everyone clear so far?
Alright
Alright, good stuff, good stuff
So then, let us continue, all right?
Let us continue, brothers and sisters,
because there's more to share, right?
Because now think about it, right?
There are three stages in God's work.
First is the age of law.
You see, in the age of law, when Jehovah
God issued the laws and commandments to
let people know what sin was, God actually
took the name of Jehovah.
Jehovah was God's name for the age of law.
And what does the name Jehovah mean?
It means the God who is self-existing and
eternal.
And you know, self-existing
and eternal, it means that He has,
He existed from the
very beginning and He will exist forever.
He literally is the one true God.
Apart from Him, there are no other gods.
And this is the God who created the heaven
and the earth and all things and mankind.
And He personally guides humanity and
holds sovereignty over everything.
And then in the age of grace, that was the
very first time that God became flesh
to personally do the work of redeeming
humanity.
And His name was Jesus.
And what does Jesus stand for?
You see, in Hebrews, Jesus stands for
Emmanuel.
Which means God is with us.
Hello, Sister Deborah, welcome.
So now, brothers and sisters, when God
returns in the last days to express the
truth, to
carry out the work of judgment, to cleanse humanity.
do you think He will have a new name?
What do you think?
If in the age of law, His name was
Jehovah.
If in the age of grace, His name was Jesus
Christ.
Well, in the age of kingdom, does God have a new name in the last days, brothers and sister?
What do you think?
Will He have a new name?
Yes or no.
Yes or no, everybody.
Okay, Yannis says yes, Michael says yes,
Anthony says yes, Draco says yup.
Shanzi says yes, Clifton says yes,
Tawana says yes.
Okay, brothers and sisters, we're all on
the same page again.
Look at that.
Well, what about those who are thinking,
no?
Right?
What about the brothers and sisters who are
saying, no, he will not have a new name?
Well, I want to share something.
All right, let's read two Bible verses,
brothers and sisters.
You'll find the answer here.
In Revelation chapter 3 verses 12,
look what it's prophesied.
It says him that overcomes will I make a
pillar in the temple of my God,
and he shall go no more out.
And I will write on him the name of my God
in the name of the city of my God,
which is New Jerusalem, which comes down
out of heaven from my God.
And I will write on him my new name.
Then we have Isaiah 62.2.
The Gentiles shall see your righteousness,
and all kings your glory.
You shall be called by a new name,
which the mouth of the Lord will name.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
Based on these two verses, what do you
think?
Does God have a new name or what?
Of course he does.
Because both verses mention God having a
new name.
So since
God will have a new name,
he is obviously not
going to use the name he used in the past.
So that means when the Lord returns, he
definitely will not be called Jesus anymore.
So what is God's new name then?
Let's read.
Let's read, brothers and sisters,
okay?
I want to see whether brothers and sisters
can pick out from these verses.
I want to see whether you can understand
what these prophecies read.
The first one says, I am Alpha and Omega,
the beginning and the ending, said the Lord
which is, which was, and which is to
come, the Almighty.
Revelation 1.8.
And I heard as they were the voice of a
great multitude, and as the voice of many
waters, and as the voice of mighty
fountains.
Saying, hallelujah for the Lord God
Almighty's reigns.
Revelation 19.6.
And I heard
another out of the altar say, even so, Lord God Almighty,
true and righteous are your judgments.
Revelation 16.7.
Saying,
we give you thanks, O Lord God Almighty,
Which
are and were, and are, and are to come.
Because you have taken to you your great
power and have reigned.
Revelation 11, 17.
Brothers and
sisters, based on these four verses,
what is God's name
in the age of kingdom of the last days?
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Did anyone catch it?
Oh, Brother Michael caught it.
Anthony caught it.
Anyone catch it, brothers and sisters?
Yeah.
It's right there in front of you.
Who caught it?
Michael and Anthony so far caught it.
Clifton also caught it.
Yeah.
Anyone else?
Hmm.
What about Warren?
Dracos?
What about Eddie?
Janet?
Enrique? Kisha?
Andrea?
Debra?
Tommy?
Yanis?
Robert?
Maureen?
Alberta?
Tawana?
Pamela?
Jim?
Did you catch it?
Chauncey did.
Maureen also did.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Alberta also caught it as well.
That's right.
Brothers and sisters, God will be coming
back with the name of Almighty God.
You see?
Almighty God will be God's new name.
So, in the Age of Law, Jehovah was the
name of God.
In the Age of Grace, Jesus was the name of
God.
In the Age of Kingdom, His name will be
Almighty God.
So, speaking of this, right?
Oh, that's okay, Brother Dracos.
I had a thought.
Don't doubt yourself, my dear brother.
Don't doubt yourself.
If you feel like you're right,
you put it there, okay, brother?
It has a nice ring to it, right,
Brother Warren?
Because He's the...
He's coming back as the Almighty to
conquer all.
Yeah, it does have a nice ring to it.
Amen, everybody.
So,
perhaps some of you are probably asking,
well,
why does God need to change His name?
What is the significance of this?
Well, we will understand after reading a
few passages of words together.
All right?
So, let me send it to the group.
Let's listen to a few passages of words
together, and let's understand why.
Why does God have to take on a new name?
Right?
I think brothers and sisters may already
know, but let's listen together.
In each age, God does new work and is
called by a new name.
How could He do the same work in different
ages?
How could He cling to the old?
The name of Jesus was taken for the sake
of the work of redemption.
So, would He still be called by the same
name when He returns in the last days?
Would He still be doing the work of
redemption?
Why is it
that Jehovah and Jesus are one, yet,
they are called
by different names in different ages?
Is it not because the ages of their work
are different?
Could a single name represent God in His
entirety?
This being so, God must be called by a
different name in a different age,
and He must use the name to change the age
and to represent the age.
For no one name can fully represent God
Himself.
And
each name is able only to represent the
temporal
aspect of God's disposition in a given age.
All it needs to do is to represent His
work.
Therefore,
God can choose whatever name befits
His
disposition to represent the entire age.
Amen.
And the second one reads, In every age in
which God personally does His own work,
He
uses a name that befits the age in order
to
encapsulate the work that He intends to do.
He uses this particular name, one that
possesses the significance of that age,
to represent His disposition in that age.
This is God using the language of mankind
to express His own disposition.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
So, after reading those words,
we can understand the significance of God
taking on a new name is the fact that God
is always new and never old.
You know what that means?
God is always new and never old?
It means that God's work is always moving
forward.
God's name changes along with the age and
the work that He is doing.
So, every time God does a new stage of
work, every time He begins a new age,
He actually takes a name with specific
significance for that age, to represent
the work He is doing and the disposition
He is expressing.
So this way, we will not confine God to
just the name of Jehovah or Jesus.
And we will not define God based on our
own notions and imaginations.
Because we all know what God has and is,
is all incompatible.
You
know God is wise, He is almighty, that no
human
language simply cannot fully describe Him.
No single name could ever fully represent
everything God has and is.
So God takes on different names in
different age.
So, in the age of law, God's name was
Jehovah, which represented the work
God did in that age, in the disposition of
mercy, majesty, and wrath that He expressed.
And after that, God personally became flesh
and appeared to work as the Son of Man.
And He used the
name Jesus to do the work of redemption,
which ended the
age of law and ushered in the age of grace.
You see, the Lord Jesus showed people the
way of repentance.
He forgave their sins.
He gave them abundant grace and was ultimately
crucified to redeem all of humanity.
The name of Jesus, it represents the work
of redemption that He did in the age of
grace and the disposition of mercy,
loving kindness that He also expressed.
But in the last days, brothers and
sisters, when the Lord Jesus comes back
again, He will do so under the name of
Almighty God.
And He will usher in the age of kingdom.
He
will express the truth to carry out the
work
of judgment beginning at the house of God.
And
He does this to completely save us from sin
once and
for all, and to make a group of overcomers.
And after that, what do you think is going
to happen?
The great disasters
will run down, brothers and sisters,
to punish
the wicked, but also to reward His people.
God wants to destroy this dark,
evil, old, wicked world.
He does.
Because that's the only way that the kingdom
of Christ will finally appear on earth.
So the name Almighty, it represents God's
inherent disposition.
All that God has and is.
So in the last days, the incarnate
Almighty God, He just comes to speak.
Because only with the words will He judge
and expose our corruption.
Only with the words He will cleanse and
save us.
Only with the words He also punishes all
enemy forces of sin.
And He will establish His kingdom.
And everything is established and
accomplished through the mouth of Christ.
Which really shows, God's all mightiness.
So the name Almighty God, is actually the
most suitable for the age of kingdom.
Right?
It's very suitable, brothers and sisters.
And I actually want to give you an
example.
Let me give you an example here.
Okay?
Let's say for example, you, if you are a
teacher at a school.
How are students going to address you,
brothers and sisters?
They're going to address you as a teacher.
Right?
And if you became a doctor, then you would
be addressed as a doctor.
But
if you opened up a store and became the
owner,
then of course, you would be the boss.
You see brothers and sisters, when your
profession changes, if your title does not
change, then people are not going to know
your new profession.
So when your profession changes,
your title needs to change as well.
Even though
others call you by a different name or by a
different title,
you are still the same person, aren't you?
The same principle applies to God.
In
different era, in different ages,
God does different work
to open up the new age with a new name.
So although God's name may change,
and although His work may change,
brothers and sisters, you have to
understand something.
Welcome Vicki and Foylene.
God's essence, that will never change.
Almighty God, Jesus, Jehovah, it's still
the same God doing God's work.
In other words, God's essence,
that will never change.
But yes, God's name, that can change.
That can change, brothers and sisters.
Okay?
Does that make sense so far, brothers and
sisters?
Are we clear so far?
Amen.
What about others?
Clear so far, right, brothers and sisters?
Amen.
Thanks be to God.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Praise be to God.
Yeah, it'll never change, okay?
It'll never, ever, ever, ever change,
brothers and sisters.
Let's, let's listen, let's read two
passages here together.
I have two passages, okay?
Would
any brother or sister like to help me read
the first
one, and then I can read the second one?
Or I can read the first one, and someone
can read the second one, okay?
Because I know a lot of people will say,
well, Sister Thelma, doesn't the Bible
say, the Lord Jesus Christ, the same
yesterday, today, and forever?
but you see, a lot of people take
Bible verses out of context.
When the Bible says, Jesus Christ,
the same yesterday, today, and forever,
that's not referring to his name,
at all.
Instead, okay, Yanis, I'll read the first
one, and I'll, you can read the second.
Oh, Andrea, you read the first one,
and Yanis will read the second one, then.
Yeah,
you go ahead and open up your mic, Sister Andrea,
since you will read the first one.
Can you hear me?
so, brothers and sisters, when the Bible
says, Jesus Christ, the same yesterday,
today, and forever, it actually only means
God's disposition.
All right, doesn't mean his name will
never change.
Go ahead, Sister Andrea, you can read the
first one for us, my dear sis.
Where it says, there are those who say
that God is forever unchanging.
You got it.
Okay, there are those who say that God is
forever unchanging.
That is correct.
But it means that God's disposition,
and his essence are unchanging.
Changes in his name and work do not prove
that his essence has changed.
In other words, God will always be God,
and this will never change.
If you say that the work of God is
unchanging, then would it be possible for
his 6,000 year management plan to come to
an end?
You only know that God is forever
unchanging.
But do you know that God is always new and
never old?
If the
work of God never changed, could he have
led
mankind all the way to the present day?
If God were forever unchanging,
why did he already do the work of two ages?
The words, God is forever unchanging,
refer to what God inherently has and is.
Regardless, you cannot confine the work of
6,000 years to a single point,
or circumscribe it with dead words.
Such is the ignorance of man.
God is not as simple as man imagines,
and his work cannot linger in any one age.
Jehovah, for example, cannot always stand
for the name of God.
God can also do his work under the name of
Jesus.
This is a sign that God's work is always
progressing in a forward direction.
Beautiful reading, my dear sister.
Brother Yannis, would you like to read the
second one?
Yes.
God is always God, and he will never
become Satan.
Satan is always Satan, and he will never
become God.
God's wisdom, God's wonderness,
God's righteousness, and God's majesty
shall never change.
His essence and what he has, and his
faithfulness shall never ever change.
As for his work, it is progressing in a
forward direction.
Let's go deeper.
It is always God's work.
He is always new, and never always old.
In every age, God assumes a new name.
In every age, he does new work.
And
in every age, he allows us created beings
to see
his new intentions and new dispositions.
Amen.
Beautiful reading.
Sister Pinky, make sure to mute your mic.
Okay, Pinky?
All right.
Make sure to mute your mic, Pinky.
Amen.
Great reading, both Sister Andrea and
Brother Yannis.
Great reading.
So from these two passages, it's clear,
right?
God is eternally unchanging.
But this is talking about God's
disposition in essence, not his name.
Hello.
So even though God does different work,
and takes different names in different
ages, while saving humanity, God's essence
will never change.
God is always God, brothers and sisters.
Right?
And God's almightiness, righteousness,
and holiness, that never changes as well.
So in other words,
whether God uses the name of Jehovah, or
Jesus, or Almighty
God, his essence does not change at all.
It's always the same God doing the same
work.
All right?
You cannot, cannot break them apart.
Okay, brothers and sisters?
You see, the
relationship between the three stages, it
really is done
by one God, going deeper stage by stage.
So the age of law, it's like the plowing
season.
It's the beginning of the salvation,
so people can know what sin is.
And the age of grace, it's the sowing
season.
It's the continuation of the salvation to
forgive our sins.
And the age of kingdom is the reaping
season.
That's the complete salvation.
It is to remove our sins.
And all this work is done by one God.
You see, the age of law, the plowing
season, that was Jehovah God.
The age of grace, the sowing season,
that was Jesus Christ.
The age of kingdom, the reaping season,
that's Almighty God.
They're all the same God, brothers and
sisters.
All right?
They're all the same God.
The three stages of God's work, the age of
law, the age of grace, the age of kingdom.
Yeah.
Different ages, but same God.
Right?
Sister Andrea says, why did he have all
these names to refer to himself?
It's because of the work that he does,
Sister Andrea.
Different, different generation,
my beloved sister.
Different generation.
The age of law, think about it.
That was the Israelites.
The age of grace, that was the Jewish
people.
The age of kingdom, that's all of us now.
Still God, just different generation.
So the first stage, that was the age of
law.
Jehovah God issued the laws and
commandments to guide people in their
lives and to make them repent,
sorry, to make them aware of sin.
The second stage was the age of grace.
The Lord Jesus was crucified to redeem all
of humanity, allowing people to confess
and repent their sins.
And the third stage is the age of kingdom.
Almighty
God will express all the truth to
judge
and to cleanse people's sinful nature.
Right?
To enable us to be purified and to enter
the kingdom of God.
You see, brothers and sisters,
all the work is done by one God.
Amen.
Brothers and sisters, everyone clear so
far?
Everyone clear so far?
The fact that God's name changes when he
comes back again?
It has to, right?
Because he's changing his work.
Because think about it.
If he came
with the name of Jesus, then people would
still think that
he's trying to forgive us, but he's not.
Right?
He's trying to cleanse and purify us.
So the fact that he changes his name and
the age and the work, it goes to show
that, wow, God is here now to end his
work, to cleanse and to purify mankind.
But let me bring up something,
brothers and sisters.
Would you say that all three stages of
work are done by one God?
Jehovah, Jesus, and Almighty God?
Would you say it is the work of one God,
brothers and sisters?
Yes or no?
Okay.
Amen.
That's right.
That's right, brothers and sisters.
Of course it is.
Yeah, it's all done by one God.
Let's read another passage here,
okay?
Another spiritual passage.
For this one, I believe I do have an
audio.
Here we go.
From the work of Jehovah to that of Jesus,
and from the work of Jesus to that of this
current stage, these three stages cover in
a continuous thread the entire gamut of
God's management, and they are all the
work of one Spirit.
Since the creation of the world, God
has always been at work managing mankind.
He is the beginning and the end.
He is the first and the last.
And He is the one who begins an age and
the one who brings the age to an end.
The three stages
of work, in different ages and different
locations,
are unmistakably the work of one Spirit.
All those who separate these two, these
three stages, stand in opposition to God.
Now, it behooves you to understand that
all the work from the first stage until
today, is the work of one God,
the work of one Spirit.
Of this, there can be no doubt.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
You see, although the ages change,
although the names change, it's still God.
You see, the three
stages of God's work are closely linked
together,
built upon the foundation of the last one.
It progresses deeply.
Every stage is built upon the foundation
of the previous one, brothers and sisters.
It's almost like you going to school.
After elementary school is high school.
After high school is college.
After college, you go find a job,
right?
It progresses.
God's work of saving mankind also
progresses as well.
They go deeper and deeper and deeper.
And they all work together.
They're all closely connected together.
You can't leave a single one out.
And you have to really think about it,
right?
Let's try to understand, brothers and
sisters, if God did not do the work of the
age of law, humanity wouldn't even know
what sin is.
They
just live in sin, get trampled by Satan,
and
be quickly carried off and be wiped out.
If that
hadn't happened, there would be no way for
God
to even start his work in the age of grace.
And without the work of God, without
redemption in the age of grace,
humanity would have been punished for
committing way too many sins.
We wouldn't even have made it until today.
And what if there was no judgment coming
to save us?
Then we would never break free from the
bondage and the constraints of sin.
We would never be qualified to enter God's
kingdom.
And we would ultimately be destroyed for
all of our sins.
So you see,
if you take away any of these three stages,
all of us
would fall right back into Satan's hands.
And we would not be able to be cleansed.
So these three stages of work,
brothers and sisters, it really makes up
God's complete management plan to save
humanity.
Each stage is more crucial and important
than the last.
They're all carefully planned and arranged
by God to save humanity.
And this completely shows God's incredible
love and salvation for mankind.
It shows God's wisdom and almightiness.
So you see, brothers and sisters,
with the three stages going deeper,
step by step, now you can see Jehovah God,
the Lord Jesus, and Almighty God,
they're all one.
You can't separate them.
They're all one.
Even though God's name changes,
even though the method and the content of
His work changes, all three stages of work
are done by one God, brothers and sisters.
Alright?
They're all done by one God.
And how do we know?
How do we know?
You gotta focus on the truth.
Alright?
The key, brothers
and sisters, is whether He expresses
the truth and
carries out the work of saving humanity.
Whoever expresses
the truth, whoever speaks God's voice and
does the work of
saving people, that is truly God Himself.
And that is the most important key point.
Alright?
So now, think of this other question.
Let's say if someone wants to stay stuck
in the age of grace.
Let's say they don't want to accept the
age of grace.
they only accept Jesus work of redemption
They refuse the work of judgment that
Almighty God does in the age of kingdom.
Do you think they can get into God's
kingdom?
A.
I think so.
People who believe in Jesus can get into
God's kingdom no matter what.
Or B.
I don't think so.
You have to follow God's footsteps
closely.
And
you have to experience His work of judgment
in
the last days in order to be cleansed.
Or C.
I don't know.
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Ah.
Amen, Brother Anthony.
Amen, Brother Michael.
Anyone else?
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
What do you think?
If
you want to stay stuck in the age of grace,
do
you think God will put you in His kingdom?
What do you think, Andrea?
And Eddie?
Clifton?
Janet?
What do you think, Enrique?
Keisha?
Yanis?
Amen, Brother Warren.
Amen, Jim and Alberta.
What about Pamela?
Tawana?
What do you think?
If you only accept
the age of grace and reject the age of
kingdom, you really
think God will put you in His kingdom?
No.
Absolutely not, brothers and sisters.
You could see.
He won't.
He will not at all.
Absolutely not.
And that's a fact, brothers and sisters.
So now let's talk about what kind of
humanity God ultimately wants to make
through these three stages of work.
Listen up.
This is very important.
What kind of humanity God wants to gain?
Yeah, go ahead, my dear brother.
What
kind of humanity does God ultimately want
to
make through these three stages of work?
The
purpose of God's management is to gain A
group of
people who worship God and submit to him.
Although
these people have been corrupted by
Satan,
they no longer see Satan as their father.
Instead, they recognize the repulsive face
of Satan and reject it.
And they come before God to accept God's
judgment and chastisement.
They come to know
the contrast between the ugly and the holy
and to recognize
the greatness of God and the evil of Satan.
A mankind such as this will no longer serve
Satan or worship Satan or enshrine Satan.
This is because they are a group of people
who have truly been gained by God.
This is the significance of God's work of
managing mankind.
Amen.
Beautiful reading, my dear brother.
You want to know, brothers and sisters?
You see, the humanity that God ultimately
wants to gain is actually a group of
people
who can see through Satan's tricks, who
can completely
break free from Satan's corruption.
And they are a group of people who truly
understand God and God's work.
So this group of people is a higher form
of humanity than Adam and Eve.
They are a group of people who will never
be fooled by Satan again.
And they are completely gained by God.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
So from our
fellow believers, today, we've learned that, right?
God's work of managing
mankind is divided into three stages.
Now, you tell
me, for all of us who are living in the
last days,
which stage is the most critical for us?
The one that will directly decide our
final outcome and destination?
Which stage?
The age of law, the age of grace,
or the age of kingdom?
Which one of them will decide our final
destination?
The law, the grace, or the kingdom?
That's right, brother Warren.
That's right, Michael.
That's right, Yanis.
Anyone else?
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Which one will decide our final
destination?
You got it, brother Clifton.
Yeah.
There's no doubt, brothers and sisters.
The
one that will decide each of our final
destination
is no other than the age of kingdom.
You see?
So in God's management plan, there are
three stages of God's work to save mankind.
You see?
The age of law, the age of grace,
and the age of kingdom.
So when God returns in the life of God,
and in very last days, He ends the age of
grace, and He ushers in the age of
kingdom.
And he does the work of judgment beginning
with the house of God.
So
God's judgment work in the age of kingdom
is the
final stage of the three stages of work.
It's the work that concludes God's
management plan.
So
whether or not people can accept and submit
to
it directly impacts their final outcome.
Some people might say, I only believe in
Jesus.
I won't accept his return.
I'm not going to keep up with his new
work.
Is that okay?
It's not okay.
Because what is the Lord going to say?
He
will say, many will say to me in that day,
Lord,
Lord, have we not prophesied in your name?
And in your name have cast out devils?
And in your name have done many wonderful
works?
Then will I profess to them, I never knew
you.
Depart from me, you that work iniquity.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
Look at that.
A lot of people don't even get this.
You see, these people, they have believed
in the Lord their entire lives.
They have suffered a great deal.
They have held on to the name of the Lord
Jesus.
But why didn't they get the Lord's
approval in the end?
Why were they condemned as evildoers
instead?
Do you know what's really going on?
It's because they only accepted the age of
grace, the redemption work.
Right?
Yeah,
they had their sins forgiven, but they
refuse
the judgment work of the age of kingdom.
They condemn it.
They condemn it, brothers and sisters.
So their corrupt dispositions are not
cleansed.
They still rebel against God, resist God,
deny God, betray God.
Because why?
They still have a sinful nature that
cannot be resolved.
They simply are just not qualified for
God's kingdom.
They're not good enough.
Because they have Satan's poison,
which is not allowed in the kingdom.
Because
if Satan's poison gets in the kingdom,
oh
boy, oh boy, that'll be trouble again.
We'll have to start all over again.
You see, brothers and sisters,
so rejecting God's work of judgment in the
last days, rejecting Christ of the last
days and refusing his salvation of the
last days, that is the very proof of one's
condemnation.
The outcome is to fall into perdition and
to be destroyed.
They'll forever lose the chance to be
saved and enter the kingdom of heaven.
But on the flip side, those who truly
believe in God, those who long for the
appearance of God, yeah, they will be
cleansed.
And they will enter the next stage with
God.
And they will enjoy eternal rest with God.
Now
you see, brothers and sisters, you see
the
world for what it is right now, don't you?
Yes, you do.
You see the world for But it is, my beloved
brothers and sisters, it's horrible.
Disasters are getting worse and worse.
Isn't it?
Hurricanes, earthquakes, plagues and wars,
it's all happening all over.
So God's 6,000 year management plan is
actually coming to an end.
Look!
The ark is coming to a close, brothers and
sisters.
We don't have much time left.
And that is why, brothers and sisters,
seeking God's appearance and His work is
the most important thing that we can do
right now.
It's exactly why we're holding these
online gatherings, right?
That's right, Brother Warren, everything
is a mess.
That's why we're here.
We're here to seek the truth.
We're here to hold on gatherings,
to really awaken us.
So no matter how busy you are,
I really hope that you'll stay with us and
finish these eight days of studies.
We've got five more days, brothers and
sisters, okay?
Five more days, my dear brothers and
sisters.
So I hope that you will come back
tomorrow.
Because tomorrow, we are going to start a
new topic.
And
honestly, tomorrow's topic is going to be
the
most important one out of all of the eight.
You see, tomorrow's topic is going to
be...
Have you heard the voice of God?
Have you?
Especially
because the Lord Jesus says, My sheep
hear
my voice, I know them, they follow me.
And also, behold, I stand at the door and
knock.
If any man hear my voice, and open the door I will come in.
So if we truly are God's sheep,
and if we want to welcome the Lord's
return, we need to be able to learn how to
recognize God's voice.
And that means God's voice, it probably
has its own unique characteristics.
So here are some key questions that we are
going to explore tomorrow night.
We're going to talk about what are the
characteristics of God's voice?
And how can we recognize God's voice and
welcome the Lord's return?
So
this topic is directly connected to whether
we
can be wise virgins and welcome the Lord.
And even it has to do with our eternal
life.
So brothers and sisters, I know some of
you are older than me.
I know many of you have believed in the
Lord all your lifetime.
I know many of you are waiting for his
return.
So don't you want to welcome the Lord
while you're still alive?
Would you really want to miss the chance
to recognize him when he comes back?
Of course not, right?
So if you've been longing for the Lord's
return, if you want to be a wise virgin
who welcomes his return, then I don't want
you to miss him.
Alright?
You don't want to end up like a foolish
virgin, brothers and sisters.
If you really want to know whether you're
truly one of God's sheep, then tomorrow,
you're going to find the answers.
So really,
no matter how busy we are, I really hope
that no one
will miss tomorrow night's amazing topic.
Yeah, I'm praying.
I'm praying that
God will make a way for each of you because
you're going
to hear something that may surprise you.
But at the same time, it's going to bring
you a lot of joy.
So who's coming tomorrow, brothers and
sisters?
Who's
coming tomorrow to hear this great
news
that we've got to share with all of you?
I hope you will, brothers and sisters.
Amen.
Yeah. Yeah.
Amen, Yanis.
Amen, Shanzi.
Amen.
Amen, Warren.
Amen, Clifton.
I'll be here.
And I will call all of you tomorrow to
make sure that you join, okay?
You don't want to miss this great news,
brothers and sisters, because after
tomorrow, we're going to move on to a
whole new group, an advanced group,
which I will continue to share more
mysteries with you.
Alright?
So I hope you'll be here tomorrow.
Yeah, we're going to hear a great topic
that you don't want to miss.
Amen.
With
that being said, brothers and sisters, does
anyone
have any questions about tonight's topic?
Is everyone clear of tonight's topic,
brothers and sisters?
We're all clear, right?
Okay.
If we are clear, then why don't we go
ahead and do an ending prayer.
Alright?
Let's quiet our hearts before God.
Praise be to God.
Amen.
Dear Heavenly Father, dear God, we thank
you for another wonderful topic, dear God.
Thank you for opening up our eyes and
helping us understand your management
plan, how it consists of three stages,
dear God, and how we're still waiting for
the third stage, which is the age of
kingdom, to completely cleanse and purify us.
We are greatly thankful and so blessed to
be here, dear God.
And we would have done it without you.
Thank
you for encouraging us to be here to
worship
you, especially in these times, dear God.
We see the world for what it is and it's
not pretty.
It's getting more wicked by the day.
But here we are, dear God.
Here we're seeking the truth.
We're understanding what does it take to
enter the kingdom of heaven.
And that is truly by welcoming your return
and by seeking the truth, dear God.
So we thank you for all that you do for
each and every single one of our lives.
And as we
depart from this fellowship group, I pray
that our
hearts can continue to be quiet before you.
We know that we are imperfect human
beings, dear Lord.
And I just pray that you continue to lead
and to guide us every single day.
Dear God, we know we're imperfect and
that's why we're seeking you.
We're seeking you because we know.
We know we cannot enter the kingdom of
heaven how we are.
We know that we still need a
transformation.
And we know that you come back to
transform mankind.
So please, dear God, continue to knock on
the door of our hearts, dear Lord.
Don't give up on us, dear Lord.
And I pray that all of us also cannot give
up on you.
Let's continue seeking the truth wholeheartedly until we find. Until we welcome you.
So dear God, we give you all the praise,
all the honor, and all the glory.
In your precious, righteous, holy name,
Jesus Christ, we pray.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Brothers and sisters, very good sharing,
everybody, okay?
Good sharing, my beloved brothers and
sisters.
I can't wait to share the great news with
all of you tomorrow.
So please be here or be square,
all right?
I really, really can't wait to share this
incredible topic.
So I hope everyone will make the time,
okay?
I hope everyone has a wonderful night
ahead of them.
May God bless you.
If you have any
questions, if you have any prayer requests,
please feel free to get
a hold of me, okay, brothers and sisters?
Amen.
Good night, everybody.
Good night, Yanis.
Good night, Anthony and Michael.
Good night, Warren.
Good night, Ryan, Sean.  Chauncey and Alberta,
Tawan.
Good night, Clifton.
Good night, everyone.
Good night, Alberta.
Good night, brothers and sisters.
Good night, Maureen.
God bless, okay?
Yes, have a great night, everybody.
Amen.
Thanks be to God.
Bye for now, everyone.